[{"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110305pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["UH", ",", "PRP", "RB", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "."], "qSentId": 12, "question": "How have you avoided becoming Charlie Sheen?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "VBD", "VBG", "NNP", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 13, "answer": "Oh, you just don't know.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Charlie Sheen"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110305pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "RBR", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 20, "question": "Ladies, how have you managed to avoid ever doing an interview together?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "VBN", "TO", "VB", "RB", "VBG", "DT", "NN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 21, "answer": "I guess we're just clever in that way.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110305pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "VBZ", "RB", "VBN", "PRP", ",", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 22, "question": "And we wanted to stay friends, you know?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "PRP", "VBD", "TO", "VB", "NNS", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "."], "aSentId": 23, "answer": "Nobody has ever asked us, Piers.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110305pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "DT", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 36, "question": "Oh, you're in love with him?", "question_pos_tagged": ["UH", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 37, "answer": "I DM you all the time.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110305pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 43, "question": "How -- sitting here together, how do you feel about doing a joint interview?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", ":", "VBG", "RB", "RB", ",", "WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "VBG", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 44, "answer": "Well, it's really fun.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["England"]}, "docId": "110305pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 52, "question": "Oh, you did?", "question_pos_tagged": ["UH", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "."], "aSentId": 53, "answer": "We did an interview in England together.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110305pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 60, "question": "I loved it when you asked Hugh Hefner's girlfriend, 23, Hugh Hefner, 83, and what did she see in him?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "PRP", "WRB", "PRP", "VBD", "NNP", "NNP", "POS", "NN", ",", "CD", ",", "NNP", "NNP", ",", "CD", ",", "CC", "WP", "VBD", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 61, "answer": "Yes.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Hugh Hefner", "Hugh Hefner"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110305pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["JJ", "NNS", "IN", "CD", "JJR", "IN", "CD", "VBZ", "IN", "CD", "."], "qSentId": 62, "question": "What did you make of that?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBD", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 63, "answer": "Twenty-three goes into 83 more than 83 goes into 23.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110305pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 75, "question": "You think so?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 76, "answer": "Yes.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110305pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "."], "qSentId": 80, "question": "Does anyone care, do you think?", "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "NN", "NN", ",", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 81, "answer": "No.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110305pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 95, "question": "Is that what it is, good genes?", "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "IN", "WP", "PRP", "VBZ", ",", "JJ", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 96, "answer": "Yes.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110305pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["UH", ",", "PRP$", "NNP", ",", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "CD", "."], "qSentId": 102, "question": "You have not exposed your face to the sun in how long?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBN", "PRP$", "NN", "TO", "DT", "NN", "IN", "WRB", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 103, "answer": "Oh, my God, since I was 20.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110305pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "VBZ", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "VBG", "DT", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 111, "question": "Really?", "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "aSentId": 112, "answer": "That's because I'm at my computer writing all the time.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110305pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["UH", ",", "DT", ",", "DT", ",", "DT", ",", "DT", "."], "qSentId": 130, "question": "I mean, have you had any real cataclysmic fallings out?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "VBP", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "JJ", "JJ", "NNS", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 131, "answer": "Oh, no, no, no, no.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110305pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["CC", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "VB", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 137, "question": "Which one was that?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WDT", "CD", "VBD", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 138, "answer": "And he didn't like you.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110305pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 147, "question": "He was number three, right?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "NN", "CD", ",", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 148, "answer": "Yes.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Joan"]}, "docId": "110305pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "TO", "VB", "CC", "NNP", "VBD", "TO", "VB", "."], "qSentId": 184, "question": "What were you like together when you were young sisters?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBD", "PRP", "IN", "DT", "WRB", "PRP", "VBD", "JJ", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 185, "answer": "Well, I used to write and Joan used to illustrate.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110305pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBD", "."], "qSentId": 188, "question": "And is that why you sort of developed the creative writing?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "VBZ", "IN", "WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "VBN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 189, "answer": "I guess I did.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110305pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP$", "NNS", "VBD", "RB", ",", "RB", "JJ", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 200, "question": "What were you -- what were your parents like?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBD", "PRP", ":", "WP", "VBD", "PRP$", "NNS", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 201, "answer": "Well, our parents were very, very different from each other.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110305pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NN", "DT", "CD", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 208, "question": "Were you?", "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 209, "answer": "Hence the five husbands.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110305pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": [":", "RB", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 248, "question": "... is the way to put it, right?", "question_pos_tagged": [":", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "TO", "VB", "PRP", ",", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 249, "answer": "... very much.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110305pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "NN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 250, "question": "Is that -- is that the wrong way -- that's the right way around, right?", "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "IN", ":", "VBZ", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", ":", "IN", "POS", "DT", "NN", "NN", "IN", ",", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 251, "answer": "That is the right way 'round.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110305pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 260, "question": "And do you remember when Jackie went out with Marlon Brando?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "WRB", "NNP", "VBD", "IN", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 261, "answer": "Yes, I do, actually.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Jackie", "Marlon Brando"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110305pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "RB", ":"], "qSentId": 268, "question": "You and Marlon?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "CC", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 269, "answer": "Yes, well...", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Marlon"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110305pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", ",", "DT", "."], "qSentId": 280, "question": "Really?", "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "aSentId": 281, "answer": "No, no.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Joan"]}, "docId": "110305pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": [":", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "NN", "TO", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "NNP", "MD", "VB", "PRP", "TO", "VB", "."], "qSentId": 294, "question": "Can you tell that I'm a writer?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 295, "answer": "... a certain temporary nature to the relationship that I don't think Joan would like you to convey.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110305pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 306, "question": "What, for me?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", ",", "IN", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 307, "answer": "Yes.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110305pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["CC", "JJ", "DT", "JJ", ",", "JJ", ",", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 314, "question": "Paul Newman?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 315, "answer": "And such a nice, sweet, down-to-earth person.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Paul Newman"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110305pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "JJ", ",", "CC", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "CC", "VBP", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 322, "question": "Who would your choice be?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "MD", "VB", "NN", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 323, "answer": "Well, I was very young, but I would skulk around these parties and watch people.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110305pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": [":", "PRP", "VBD", "PDT", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 325, "question": "Because he was huge, right?", "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP", "VBD", "JJ", ",", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 326, "answer": "... he was such a bad ass.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"DATE": ["1994"]}, "docId": "110305pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "IN", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP$", "CD", "IN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 359, "question": "What am I doing, putting my arm up?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBG", ",", "VBG", "PRP$", "NN", "RP", "."], "aSentId": 360, "answer": "Well, that was a clip from your 1994 workout video.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110305pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 363, "question": "What, do the splits?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", ",", "VBP", "DT", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 364, "answer": "Yes.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110305pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 370, "question": "Do you?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 371, "answer": "Yes.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110305pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "TO", "VB", "PRP", ",", "VBZ", "."], "qSentId": 373, "question": "Didn't you do the splits?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "RB", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 374, "answer": "No, I decided not to do them, yes.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110305pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "DT", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "RB", ",", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", ":", "JJ", "IN", "DT", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "VBG", ":", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "JJ", "VBZ", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 380, "question": "Because the pressure is so unbearable, isn't it?", "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "DT", "NN", "VBZ", "RB", "JJ", ",", "VBZ", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 381, "answer": "Well, no, I don't think so, because I don't -- first of all, I think that staying -- trying to look young is ridiculous.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110305pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "."], "qSentId": 391, "question": "I mean, cut to the -- have either of you two ladies ever succumbed to the scalpel?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "VBD", "TO", "DT", ":", "VBP", "JJR", "IN", "PRP", "CD", "NNS", "RB", "VBN", "TO", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 392, "answer": "No.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110305pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP", "VBP", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 399, "question": "Why have you been able to resist it when so many others have fallen by the wayside?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "VBN", "JJ", "TO", "VB", "PRP", "WRB", "RB", "JJ", "NNS", "VBP", "VBN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 400, "answer": "Because we're needle-phobic.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110305pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "CC", "PRP", "VBZ", ",", "CC", "PRP$", "NN", "VBD", "."], "qSentId": 402, "question": "Are you really?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 403, "answer": "Well, I am, and she is, and our mother was.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110305pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ":"], "qSentId": 440, "question": "I look at you and I see healthy vitality, you know?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "IN", "PRP", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", "JJ", "NN", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "."], "aSentId": 441, "answer": "Well...", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110305pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 442, "question": "You're sort of a get-up-and-go ladies, aren't you?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "NN", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NNS", ",", "VBP", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 443, "answer": "Yes.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110305pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "NN", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "IN", "DT", "."], "qSentId": 483, "question": "Really?", "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "aSentId": 484, "answer": "I don't put anything on my face at all.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110305pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP", "RB", ":", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "JJ", "IN", "DT", "."], "qSentId": 494, "question": "Well, how have I got good skin?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "VBD", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 495, "answer": "Because you just -- because you shave, first of all.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110305pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ":", "DT", "."], "qSentId": 502, "question": "You had Botox?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 503, "answer": "ORGAN: No.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110305pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "."], "qSentId": 530, "question": "I mean, that was the movie really that propelled you into super stardom, wasn't it?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "IN", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "RB", "IN", "VBN", "PRP", "IN", "NN", "NN", ",", "VBD", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 531, "answer": "I guess.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110305pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "NN", "VBD", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP$", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 552, "question": "And what did he say to (inaudible)?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "WP", "VBD", "PRP", "VB", "TO", "VB", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 553, "answer": "Yes, somebody asked if he read my books.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110305pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "."], "qSentId": 564, "question": "Did you ever think it was going to be that huge?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "RB", "VBP", "PRP", "VBD", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "IN", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 565, "answer": "No idea at all.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110305pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "PRP$", "."], "qSentId": 592, "question": "I mean, how like Alexis have you been over the years?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "WRB", "IN", "NNP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBN", "RP", "DT", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 593, "answer": "Well, I look like her.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Alexis"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110305pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "IN", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 598, "question": "Do you flare up like that?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "RP", "IN", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 599, "answer": "Not that much.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110305pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", ",", "RB", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 600, "question": "Do you think I do?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBP", "."], "aSentId": 601, "answer": "No, not really.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Gemini"]}, "docId": "110305pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 604, "question": "Have you two ever had a fight like what we just saw?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "CD", "RB", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "IN", "WP", "PRP", "RB", "VBD", "."], "aSentId": 605, "answer": "She's a Gemini.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110305pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "."], "qSentId": 609, "question": "You've never rolled around on the floor?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBN", "IN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 610, "answer": "No.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110305pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", ",", "TO", "VB", "JJS", "."], "qSentId": 614, "question": "Us rolling on the floor?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBG", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 615, "answer": "Probably, to be honest.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110305pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["CC", "RB", "PRP", "VBD", "RP", "DT", "DT", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "PRP", "VBZ", "."], "qSentId": 618, "question": "No, she -- I can't remember -- one of us jumped on the other one's back once when we were very, very young, and I think it was I who jumped on your back or you jumped on mine?", "question_pos_tagged": ["DT", ",", "PRP", ":", "PRP", "MD", "RB", "VB", ":", "CD", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "CD", "POS", "NN", "RB", "WRB", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", ",", "RB", "JJ", ",", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBD", "PRP", "WP", "VBD", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "CC", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 619, "answer": "And then I cut off all the buttons off all her clothes.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110305pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "IN", "POS", "WP", "PRP", "VBP", "."], "qSentId": 633, "question": "How can you ever be friendly with anyone again after that?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "MD", "PRP", "RB", "VB", "RB", "IN", "NN", "RB", "IN", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 634, "answer": "Well, that's what I mean.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110305pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "NNP", ":", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "VBN", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 646, "question": "Is there any way back for this friendship, do you think?", "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "EX", "DT", "NN", "RB", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 647, "answer": "OAN COLLINS: I don't think it's ever been a friendship.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110305pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "DT", "VBZ", "IN", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 660, "question": "Why haven't they given me one?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "RB", "PRP", "VBN", "PRP", "CD", "."], "aSentId": 661, "answer": "Well, this is for you.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110305pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["CC", "PRP", "VBZ", "``", "IN", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 663, "question": "Oh, it is?", "question_pos_tagged": ["UH", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "."], "aSentId": 664, "answer": "And it says \"that sounds like a challenge.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110305pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["IN", "NN", "VBD", "."], "qSentId": 675, "question": "Oh, really?", "question_pos_tagged": ["UH", ",", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 676, "answer": "So stay tuned.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110305pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["MD", "VB", "."], "qSentId": 681, "question": "Really?", "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "aSentId": 682, "answer": "Could be.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110305pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "NNP", ":", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBN", ":", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBN", ":", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBN", "."], "qSentId": 683, "question": "Have we got a little scoop there?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "RB", "NN", "EX", "."], "aSentId": 684, "answer": "OAN COLLINS: I'm not allowed -- I'm not allowed -- I'm not allowed.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110305pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "VBN", "IN", "NNP", ",", "VBG", "."], "qSentId": 690, "question": "Is \"Dynasty\" coming back?", "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "``", "JJ", "''", "VBG", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 691, "answer": "It's been on Twitter, darling.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110305pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "MD", "RB", "VB", "."], "qSentId": 692, "question": "Yeah, but is it properly coming back?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "CC", "VBZ", "PRP", "RB", "VBG", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 693, "answer": "I can't say.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110305pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "MD", "RB", "VB", "VBG", "IN", "PRP", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 694, "question": "Are you going to be reprising?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "VBG", "."], "aSentId": 695, "answer": "Well, I wouldn't be talking about it if I wasn't.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110305pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 710, "question": "Does sex get better with age, do you think?", "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "NN", "VB", "JJR", "IN", "NN", ",", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 711, "answer": "You tell us.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110305pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "JJ", "NN", "NN", ":", "NN", ":", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 717, "question": "I know, it's great, isn't it?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "JJ", ",", "VBZ", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 718, "answer": "The classic gong buster (ph) material.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110305pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 719, "question": "Right?", "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "aSentId": 720, "answer": "Yes.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110305pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NN", "."], "qSentId": 732, "question": "How much of all the stuff that you write about have you actually partaken in?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "JJ", "IN", "DT", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "JJ", "PRP", "RB", "VBP", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 733, "answer": "Everything.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110305pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 734, "question": "Seriously?", "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "aSentId": 735, "answer": "Yes.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110305pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 736, "question": "It's all based on your experience?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "VBN", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 737, "answer": "Well, I was a wild child.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110305pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 758, "question": "A thousand?", "question_pos_tagged": ["DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 759, "answer": "Yes.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110305pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "MD", "VB", "IN", "NN", "PRP", ",", "CC", "RB", "PRP", "VBD", "TO", "VB", "DT", "JJ", "NNS", "IN", "RB", "WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "IN", ",", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "DT", "NN", ":", "CC", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 774, "question": "Why do you like it?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "IN", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 775, "answer": "You can sort of express yourself, and also I wanted to get a few followers because so when I have a book out, because I'm writing a book -- but it's not a novel.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110305pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "."], "qSentId": 785, "question": "What is your address?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 786, "answer": "JoanCollinsOBE.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110305pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 790, "question": "And what is your address?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "WP", "VBZ", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 791, "answer": "JackieJCollins.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110305pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP", "MD", ":", "IN", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "PRP", ",", "VBZ", "."], "qSentId": 841, "question": "What was mine?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBD", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 842, "answer": "If I can -- if I can correct you, yes.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110305pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ":", "RB", "DT", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "VBN", "IN", "WP", "MD", "VB", "DT", "JJ", "NN", ",", "CC", "DT", "RB", "VBG", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 857, "question": "Really?", "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "aSentId": 858, "answer": "ORGAN: So all of you have been tarred with what could be a good brush, or a potentially irritating brush.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110305pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["EX", "VBZ", "NN", "JJ", "IN", "VBG", "VBN", "TO", "VB", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 862, "question": "Is that all good?", "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 863, "answer": "There is nothing bad about being compared to awesome actors.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110305pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBZ", "VBG", "."], "qSentId": 865, "question": "Does it put huge pressure on you when you get this label, you are the next huge superstar and they name somebody you should be like?", "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "PRP", "VBD", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "NN", "CC", "PRP", "VBD", "NN", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 866, "answer": "Yes, I think it's terrifying.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110305pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "JJ", "TO", "PRP", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 873, "question": "Is it all it's cracked up to be?", "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "PRP", "DT", "PRP", "VBZ", "VBN", "RP", "TO", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 874, "answer": "I don't know, I mean, I feel I'm very new to it still.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110305pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "PRP$", "NN", "CC", "NNS", "WP", "PRP", ":", "NN", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 878, "question": "What is -- what is that -- what is that look and behavior?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", ":", "WP", "VBZ", "IN", ":", "WP", "VBZ", "IN", "NN", "CC", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 879, "answer": "Well, I think especially your publicist and people who you -- work on your team.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110305pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 903, "question": "How do you mean?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 904, "answer": "In every sense.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110305pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 915, "question": "... does the originality go?", "question_pos_tagged": [":", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 916, "answer": "Yes, really.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110305pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["UH", ",", "PRP", "RB", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "."], "qSentId": 928, "question": "How is it -- never mind Brad Pitt, who's a bastion of decency, but how have you avoided becoming Charlie Sheen?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBZ", "PRP", ":", "RB", "VBP", "NNP", "NNP", ",", "WP", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", ",", "CC", "WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "VBD", "VBG", "NNP", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 929, "answer": "Oh, you just don't know.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Brad Pitt", "Charlie Sheen"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110305pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": [":", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 934, "question": "Ladies?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "aSentId": 935, "answer": "... a kite right now.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110305pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "NN", "IN", "."], "qSentId": 937, "question": "Have we all got a secret Charlie on our hands?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "DT", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "NNP", "IN", "PRP$", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 938, "answer": "Yes, watch out.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Charlie"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110305pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "WRB", ":", "WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", ":"], "qSentId": 948, "question": "Are -- are you saying this is me?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ":", "VBP", "PRP", "VBG", "DT", "VBZ", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 949, "answer": "I'm saying how -- how do you avoid...", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110305pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBP", "TO", "VB", ":", "PRP", "VBP", "TO", "VB", "IN", "NN", "NNS", "CC", ":", "CC", "CD", "NN", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "VB", ",", "NN", ",", "JJ", "IN", "DT", ",", "PRP", "DT", "VBN", "RP", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 951, "question": "Well, how do you avoid that when it's so obviously available if you want it?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "DT", "WRB", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "RB", "JJ", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 952, "answer": "Well, like I said, I think you have to go -- you have to kind of set parameters and -- and one thing I didn't realize, look, first of all, we all signed up for this gig.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Cate Blanchett"]}, "docId": "110305pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "PRP$", "IN", ",", "CC", "NNP", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 969, "question": "Who are your -- your idols in the business?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP$", ":", "PRP$", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 970, "answer": "I've said her before, but Cate Blanchett.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110305pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "."], "qSentId": 974, "question": "You didn't, did you?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "RB", ",", "VBD", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 975, "answer": "I did.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110305pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 976, "question": "(INAUDIBLE) on the plane (INAUDIBLE), right?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NN", "NNP", "NNP", "IN", "DT", "NN", ":", "NNP", ":", ",", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 977, "answer": "I knew it.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110305pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "."], "qSentId": 985, "question": "I mean, how can you sleep in a serene way as one who is being a great actor?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "WRB", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "DT", "NN", "NN", "IN", "CD", "WP", "VBZ", "VBG", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 986, "answer": "I don't know.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Kate Winslet", "Cameron Diaz"], "LOCATION": ["Drew Barrymore"]}, "docId": "110305pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["UH", ",", "RB", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "NNP", "NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "NNP", "NNP", ",", "NNP", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 993, "question": "ORGAN: What about the actresses?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ":", "WP", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 994, "answer": "Oh, well, I love Kate Winslet, I love Cameron Diaz, Drew Barrymore.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110305pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", ":", "RB", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 997, "question": "Why is it hard in the comedic world?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBZ", "PRP", "RB", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 998, "answer": "I -- well, I think that for a number of reasons.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110305pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "DT", "VBZ", "PRP$", "NN", ",", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 1017, "question": "You are lucky, aren't you?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "JJ", ",", "VBP", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 1018, "answer": "Yes, this is my life, people.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Jimmy Stewart"]}, "docId": "110305pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBD", "DT", "RB", "JJ", "NNP", "NNP", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 1021, "question": "Who -- who are your great idols in the film business?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", ":", "WP", "VBP", "PRP$", "JJ", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "NN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 1022, "answer": "I've always had a really big Jimmy Stewart thing.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110305pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "JJR", "IN", "DT", "NN", "NN", "PRP", ":", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "WP", "VBZ", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "NN", "IN", "NN", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 1029, "question": "Is it harder though to do that?", "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "PRP", "JJR", "IN", "TO", "VB", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 1030, "answer": "No, it's easier in a way cause you -- you know, you have someone who is, you know, kind of captaining the ship.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110305pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NN", "."], "qSentId": 1042, "question": "Really?", "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "aSentId": 1043, "answer": "Mm-hmm.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110305pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "VBN", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 1044, "question": "What about your friend's boobs?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "POS", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 1045, "answer": "Well, he has already seen them.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110305pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NN", "."], "qSentId": 1046, "question": "Really?", "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "aSentId": 1047, "answer": "Mm-hmm.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110305pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "."], "qSentId": 1060, "question": "Did I?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 1061, "answer": "I tried.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110305pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "."], "qSentId": 1088, "question": "Wendy, will you marry me?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 1089, "answer": "No.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110305pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "."], "qSentId": 1096, "question": "How did this happen?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 1097, "answer": "I don't know.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110305pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBD", ":", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", ":", "PRP", "VBD", "VBG", "RB", "IN", "DT", "NN", "VBD", "."], "qSentId": 1103, "question": "And what was the moment where things sort of got cemented?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "WP", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "WRB", "NNS", "VBP", "IN", "NN", "VBN", "."], "aSentId": 1104, "answer": "Well, I was -- I mean, it was after -- we started dating actually after the movie wrapped.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110305pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 1109, "question": "Can I be honest with you about something?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "JJS", "IN", "PRP", "IN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 1110, "answer": "Yes.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110305pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 1112, "question": "Oh, really?", "question_pos_tagged": ["UH", ",", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 1113, "answer": "Yes.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110305pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "RB", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 1121, "question": "What is it really like?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "PRP", "RB", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 1122, "answer": "It's just so bizarre.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110305pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "IN", "."], "qSentId": 1133, "question": "How can you be with her?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "PRP$", "."], "aSentId": 1134, "answer": "It's so awkward.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110305pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "JJ", "IN", "POS", ":"], "qSentId": 1151, "question": "The rule -- the rule is no tongue?", "question_pos_tagged": ["DT", "NN", ":", "DT", "NN", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 1152, "answer": "I'm pretty sure that's...", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110305pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "."], "qSentId": 1160, "question": "Did he -- did he break that rule?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", ":", "VBD", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 1161, "answer": "He did.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110305pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "IN", "VBD", "PRP$", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 1163, "question": "Really?", "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "aSentId": 1164, "answer": "I think that was his tactic.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110305pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "NN", "MD", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 1170, "question": "So you're a serial rule-breaker?", "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 1171, "answer": "The character would tongue-kiss.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110305pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", ":", "NNS", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "JJ", "IN", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 1198, "question": "Yes?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "aSentId": 1199, "answer": "No -- yes, she was great about it.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Chris"]}, "docId": "110305pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "WRB", ":", "WRB", "NNP", "VBD", "TO", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 1223, "question": "Anna, what would you say?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "WP", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 1224, "answer": "I think when -- when Chris proposed to me.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110305pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", ",", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 1227, "question": "On or off screen?", "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "CC", "IN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 1228, "answer": "Both, actually.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110305pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 1230, "question": "Was he on bended knee like the character?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "IN", "VBN", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 1231, "answer": "No way.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110305pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "MD", "VB", "PRP", "TO", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 1233, "question": "What does that mean?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "IN", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 1234, "answer": "I'll give it to you.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110305pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "JJ", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 1240, "question": "Best night of your life?", "question_pos_tagged": ["JJS", "NN", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 1241, "answer": "Well, it's just such a tough question.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}]